neither in Kazakhstan nor in Ukraine nor in
ни в Казахстане ни в Украине ни в
America And specifically in the Russian
Америке А конкретно в Российской
Federation, a citizen of the Russian Federation,
Федерации гражданин Российской Федерации
the head of the Republic, Ramzan Kadyrov,
руководитель Республики Рамзан Кадыров
declared a blood feud. Yes, citizens of the
объявил кровную Месть Да гражданам
Russian Federation, two deputies from
Российской Федерации двум депутатам от
Dagestan, someone from Ingushetia, I don’t
Дагестана кому-то там от Ингушетии не
know, I don’t comment on this in any way,
знаю я никак это не
that is, you’re a little
комментирую то есть тебе немножко
dumb  yes
стрёмно да
Hello people conjured a spell, look at an
Приветик народ наколдовал смотрите
interesting
интересного
interlocutor You're just conjuring Yes, it
собеседника Ты колдуешь просто Да просто
was just some kind of game, I say so let's
какая-то дичь была я говорю так давайте
do it now I'll do it so that I have a good
сделаем сейчас я покол чтобы был хороший
interlocutor and now I'm
собеседник и вот
caught I'm from Almaty Where are you
попался Я я из Алмааты Вы
from And I'm from Tambov from Tambov the boy
откуда А я из Тамбова из Тамбова мальчик
wants a scoreboard
хочет табло
ta yes yes  yes What are you talking about
та да да да О чём общаетесь
today Well, I see you are in Kazakhstan
сегодня Ну вот я смотрю вы в Казахстане
now
сейчас
Yes, by the way, by the way, I really
Да я кстати я кстати мне очень
liked your conversation with this
понравилась твоя беседа с этим с
Latvian who worked on the ship And you were
Латыш который на пароходе работал А ты
directly watching the Stream
прямо Стрим
Yes, I was sitting in the jacuzzi I also
смотрел Да я сидел в джакузи Я тоже
wanted to get you into
хотел тебя попасть во
something  I was crossed twice I didn’t see
что-то меня два раза перес Я не видел
you I guess I just had such a
тебя я Прикинь у меня просто была такая
hot face Red you didn’t recognize
морда горячая Красная ты нар не узнал
the people damn it We missed old
блин народ Мы это мы пропустили старого
Askold he was in the jacuzzi wanted to howl in chat
аскольда он в джакузи хотел в чат
roulette That would have been a shock
рулетку выть Это был бы шок
content yes Well here you are with
контент да Ну вот ты вот ты с ним
talked to him I was tired of it for a long time and you
разговаривал Мне надоело долго а ты
stream
стримишь
somewhere Well, I’m recording a video but Well, you
где-то Ну я записываю видео но Ну ты ты
said you have videos on Yandex or somewhere
говорил у тебя там на Яндекс или где-то
Well, I thought that you
видосы Ну я думал что ты
had streams, we’re just like that, like with a jacuzzi
стримы есть мы прямо так типа с джакузи
you stream Duma in general fire content Well you  You
стримишь Дума вообще огонь контент Ну ты
can also sit like that
тоже так можешь посидеть
and Well, girls, put them in the chat plus
и А ну девчонки поставьте в чатик плюс
who would like to see Anro’s father’s stream from the
кто хотел бы увидеть Стрим отца анро из
jacuzzi now, in short, there will be a bunch of types
джакузи сейчас короче куча типа будет
so Well, what’s going on there in Kazakhstan is the
так что Ну что там у тебя в Казахстане
same You know, I’m from
таже Ты знаешь я из
sme You know, I’m from
сме Ты же знаешь я из
Melnitsky Well, I’m  I know, well, you
мельницкого Ну я знаю Ну ты что вот
hung up the Kazakh flag, so what,
казахстанский флаг повесил Ну и что
tomorrow I’ll hang it up, and the day after tomorrow there will be an
завтра повешу он и послезавтра будет
Estonian flag, tomorrow it’s the flag of Moldova,
эстонский флаг завтра он флаг Молдовы
you know me here, the Pronian flag, there’s such a
меня тут знаешь пронский флаг есть такой
cool
классный
joke
анекдот
now now a joke about the Estonian
сейчас сейчас анекдот про эстонский
flag Well, in short Well, roughly
флаг Ну короче Ну грубо
speaking, in an Estonian school, the teacher
говоря в школе в эстонской вот учитель
hung it up  flag and says Tell the
повесил флаг и говорит вот Расскажите
children What does each color of
дети Что значит каждая каждый цвет
our flag mean and they ask
нашего флага и вот там спрашивают там у
one girl there But what does the
одной девочки А вот а что означает там
blue stripe mean there this is our cold
синяя полоса вотт это наше холодное
Baltic Sea and what does the white
Балтийское море а что значит белая
stripe mean and this is our
полоса а это вот наше там будущее
bright future that we believe  means the
светлое которое мы верим азначает
black stripe and this is our Soviet
чёрная полоса а это наше Советское
past there The dark one that they tortured us there
прошлое там Тёмное которое нас там
but I gathered you up and then
мучили но я тебя собрал и тут у вовочки
asks Vovochka What does the white stripe mean
спрашивает А что означает белая полоса
And this is the extreme snow of Siberia where did you
гот А это крайние снега Сибири куда вас
all go When the Russian
всех сошл Когда придёт Российская
army comes, which is not
армия что не
funny By the way, what and what  this Latvian
смешно Кстати а что а что этому Латыш
will be Now that he will now be
будет Теперь что его теперь
imprisoned,
посадят
no, maybe he should be expelled from the country I
нет може что его выдворять из страны Я
think so, he wasn’t born there, I think
думаю так не он ж там родился я думаю
that from the ship you
что с парохода вы
are talking from the ship
говорят с парохода
No, well, in general, he said correctly
Да не ну в целом-то он правильно сказал
that the
что
prosperous population of Latvia is slowly dying there
умирает процветающий Латвии население
runs different, but
бежит разны
some kind of
прит какойто бы
yes Well, they shoot down all sorts of them, well, there was an
да Ну там сбивают эти всякие ну был
arrival of old Askol Yes, you said it doesn’t
прилёт старый аскол Да ты говорил не
reach the white mountain yes Old Askol
долетает побел гору да Старый аскол
No, well, a couple of times And
Нет ну пару раз И
what do you mean, it flew into my window
что понял ты хочешь ко мне в окно
Listen, let’s say, I understood everything
влетело Слушай давай так всё я понял
Let’s say, in short, I came up with it
Давай короче я придумал
because Ramzan Kadyrov said the day before yesterday
тому что Рамзан Кадыров позавчера заявил
that he was declaring a blood revenge on some
что он объявляет кровную Месть кому-то
official from Dagestan and
там чиновнику из Дагестана и из
Ingushetia, this is their Caucasian affairs. These are
Ингушетии это их кавказские дела Это
your Russian affairs. This is
ваши российские дела Это
Russia. Well, the Caucasus is very different from the
Россия Ну Кавказ он сильно отличается от
rest of Russia, let’s say
остальной России скажем так
they are Dagestani students in Moscow
они студенты дагестанские в Москве
who come to Moscow  in all
которые приезжают в Москву на полном
seriousness they come and live in a hostel and
серьёзе приходят вот живут в общежитии и
say that you know, we are from different teips
говорят что вот знаете мы разных тейпов
and we can’t wash in the same
и нам нельзя мыться в одной
shower, organize different showers for us
душевой организуйте нам разные душе
because according to our customs we are
потому что по нашим обычаям мы
competing teips Well, childbirth and we can’t
конкурирующие тейп Ну роды и нам нельзя
wash in the same
мыться в одной
shower, that is, these are the ones they have  there
душевой то есть Вот такие у них заскоки
are jumps, count them for jumps, for Skomi, but look,
есть прикинь за скоки за Скоми но смотри
if he
если
declares blood revenge on someone, there is a
объявляет кому-то кровную Месть есть
threat to him and his family. Yes, this is from the point of
угро его и его рода Да это с точки
view of the Russian Federation. This is
зрения Российской Федерации Это
a crime. Well, until he did it,
преступление Ну пока он этого не сделал
it’s not a
это преступлением не является
crime. Look, it’s a crime,
преступление Смотри да преступление
threatening to kill is already a
угроза убийством это уже
crime  I don’t know, I don’t relate to Caucasians,
преступление Я не знаю я к кавказцам не
this is not Citizens of the Russian
отношусь это Граждане Российской
Federation.
Федерации
Well, you know, damn it, I’m not a prosecutor, I’m not a
не Ну знаешь я блин я не прокурор я не
lawyer to try them there, blood feud
адвокат чтобы там их судить кровно месть
not blood revenge. And even Russian, let
не кровного Месть А даже Русский вот
’s say you’re now in Kazakhstan and in
допустим ты вот сейчас в Казахстане и в
Roscoe in Roscoe Kazakhstan I’m in  miller
роско в роско Казахстане Я в мельником
fla Kazakhstan Well, like you, like
фла Казахстана Ну типа ты типа в
40 thousand of
Казахстане наверное приехало тысяч 40
these Russian Kazakhs and Central
вот этих русских казахстанцев и средне
Asians probably came to Kazakhstan and in their own way they are
азиатов и они по своему
very different from the
очень сильно отличаются от
locals, they are always very polite and
местных они всегда очень вежливые и
very careful in their
очень аккуратные своих
words because for any bad word
словах потому что за любое слово плохое
they can do something else to you  something
тебе могут там там ещё что-нибудь
to do That is, they are people who have lived
сделать То есть они люди которые прожили
in Kazakhstan for many years, they have such a
в Казахстане много лет они такого
mentality, they are just some kind of
менталитета они вот прямо какие-то вот
Russians with such an Eastern
скажем русские с такой Восточной
soul, again, look
душой ещё раз смотри
neither in Kazakhstan nor in Ukraine nor in
ни в Казахстане ни в Украине ни в
America. And specifically in the Russian
Америке А конкретно в Российской
Federation, a citizen of the Russian Federation is a
Федерации гражданин Российской Федерации
leader  Republic Ramzan Kadyrov
руководитель Республики Рамзан Кадыров
declared a blood feud Yes, citizens of the
объявил кровную Месть Да гражданам
Russian Federation, two deputies from
Российской Федерации двум депутатам от
Dagestan, someone there from
Дагестана кому-то там от
Ingushetia, this is not in some foreign
Ингушетии это не в какой-то зарубежной
country, this is in your Russian Federation,
стране это в вашей Российской Федерации
I don’t know, I don’t comment on this in any way,
знаю я никак это не
that is, you’re a little
комментирую то есть тебе немножко
weird,
стрёмно
but you understand, my governor -  this is
да понимаешь мой губернатор - это
a gulp with Chechnya, we don’t
глотков с чечнёй мы не
border on him, he’s the head of his republic of
граничить он там глава своей республики
his subject of the Russian Federation,
своего субъекта Российской Федерации
even on their heads. Let them walk. You know, I do
хоть на головах Пусть ходят Вот знаешь я
n’t know there that they even do it to me
не знаю там что они хоть делают меня это
in
вообще
any way. That’s me personally as a private person. I’m
никак Вот лично меня как частное лицо Я
not a judge there of the Russian Supreme Court, which is
не судья там Верховного суда российского
not constitutional.  judge, I'm not the
не конституционного судья я не
prosecutor general Hello Hello Hello Hey
генеральный прокурор Алло Алло Алло Эй
brother stop stop stop that means Wait
братуха стоп стоп стоп значит Подожди
when you talk about Ukraine you
когда рассуждать про Украину ты
say that Maidan there is
рассказываешь что там Майдан
constitutionally unconstitutional you are
конституционно не конституционно ты тут
also a judge of the Constitutional Court of Ukraine
и судья Конституционного суда Украине да
and almost the Chairman of the Verkhovna Rada
и чуть ли не председатель Верховной Рады
yes And when they asked you about something-  then
да А когда Тебя спросили про что-то
Ask for something like this right away Oh, but I, in general,
Проси ты такой сразу Ой а я же вообще
Let them be there at least for each other, I’m No, I’m
Пусть они там хоть друг друга я ж Нет я
not the constitution, another
ж не конституци другая
civilization and they have different concepts, they
цивилизация и другие у них понятия они
live absolutely in their own way, look again
живут абсолютно по-своему ещё раз смотри
That is, I understand correctly that
То есть я правильно понимаю что
you are discussing the Maidan in Ukraine  you are discussing
обсуждать Майдан в Украине ты обсуждаешь
there, you are starting the Constitution is not the
ты там начинаешь Конституция не
Constitution, but for you it is not
Конституция Да вот для тебя это не
another, but when Citizens of the Russian
другая а когда Граждане Российской
Federation Yes,
Федерации Да
one of your Russian
твоего российского одного из
regions
регио
threatens the deputies of the State Duma of the
угрожает депутатам Государственной Думы
Russian Federation, the Dagestanis for
Российской Федерации дагестанцам для
you, right away, this is a different civilization. Well, you
тебя сразу это другая цивилизация Ну
know, any Ukrainian is much closer to me
знаешь мне любой украинец гораздо ближе
than, say, a Chechen or a Dagestani  it’s
чем допустим чеченец либо дагестанец вот
like there Let him be there from Lvov
как бы там Пусть он там со Львова будет
Let him be there praying for Bandera
Пусть он там будет молиться на бандеру
to me He’s closer than these goods
мне Он ближе чем вот эти товари
So you support the war against
Так ты поддерживаешь войну против
Ukraine Yes, I don’t
Украины Да я её не
support it Well, damn it, I don’t know, it’s a
поддерживаю Ну это блин ну не знаю
forced measure I don’t know, they don’t want
вынужденная мера Я не знаю не хотят
to do it Well  here you are forced
сделать Ну вот вот вот вот вынуждены
to support the world Yes
мира поддерживаешь Да
Support Well, damn, I don’t know what we should
Поддержи Ну блин не знаю как что нам
do when
делать когда
those you said with your mouth What are the Ukrainians there for you Yes, they are
те ты сказал своим ртом Что тебе там
much closer even if they are
украинцы Да гораздо ближе даже если они
there for Bandera And so on further than there are
там за бандеру И так дальше чем там
some Dagestanis or Chechens and
какие-то дагестанцы или чеченцы да
no bombs  Dagestan is a bomb, for example, you don’t
бомби не Дагестан бомби например Укра не
know Ukraine in terms of culture, in terms of concepts,
знаешь в плане культуры в плане понятий
of course you think that the Russians there are the same,
естественно вы мне считай такие же там
roughly speaking, but these comrades,
русские грубо говоря Но вот эти товарищи
well, damn
они Ну блин
they are on their own wave and for them it’s
они свой волне и для для них это
normal to declare a blood feud, you
нормально объявить кровную Месть
know, let’s say this, I’ll say this
понимаешь давай так э я скажу так
being in  In Belgorod, this is not normal, this is
находясь в Белгороде это ненормально это
not normal for the laws of Russia, but for
ненормально для законов России но Для
them,
них
this being in Belgorod, you are not afraid of
этот находясь в Белгороде ты не боишься
some dude from Lvov because he is
какого-то чувака из Львова потому что он
far away, but you are afraid of the guys from the Caucasus.
далеко но боишься пацанов с Кавказа
No, why are you provoking me to
Да не ну а что ты провоцируешь чтобы я
say something against Kadyrov there?
что-то сказал против Кадырова меня там
nailed it down you're afraid Well, tell me I'm afraid I
прибили этого боишься Ну скажи я боюсь я
don't
не
want you want Yes you want it I want
хочу ты хочешь Да ты этого хочешь Я хочу
Yes yaho you hate me so much that you're
Да яхо ты меня так ненавидишь что ты
ready to incite Kadyrov directly, not even to
готов прямо это Кадырову натравить даже
hate him Well, that
да не то что ненавидеть Ну да это было
would be interesting No, well, Think about it, Think about it,
бы интересно Не ну Прикинь Прикинь вот
Kadyrov will take a look  there he will say Oh,
Кадыров посмотрит там скажет О это вот
I don’t like this one Let’s get
мне этот не нравится Давайте Достаньте
him, let him apologize And you’ll have
его пусть он извиняется А у тебя тут
jubilation on the stream here Here you’ll
будет ликование на стриме тут Тут целую
think about a whole topic about before that they caught everything
тему подумаешь о до этого отловили всё
well, I’m telling you, look, there are
хорошо я тебе говорю смотри есть тебя
Kadyrov’s people eating you And like, you’ll apologize
кадыровцы Да и типа ты будешь извиняться
I’ll record a video  Yes, with an appeal there to the
Я запишу ролик Да с обращением там к
Russian Federation Yes, to stop
Российской Федерации Да прекратить
means this
значит этого
Eh, it’s like persecution of this
Ээ как бы преследование вот такого
character of ours who we are currently
нашего персонажа которые сечас мы
communicating on the stream Yes, we’ll really
общаемся на стриме Да вот реально
protect, let’s join in, we’ll write in short,
защитим вступим се будем писать короче
this is also in me and for
это в меня ещ и за
this you’re rummaging around
это шаришь шаришь
No, chat chat, put a plus Yes  who is
ну чатик чатик поставьте плюс Да кто
ready to write letters like to some kind of
готов писать письма типа в какой-то в
investigative committee or even to the
следственный комитет да или там в
State Duma Yes, in support of old Askold
Госдуму Да в поддержку старого аскольда
if his
если его
Kadyrovites now have a full chat of advantages,
кадыровцев сейчас полный чат плюсов
I’m telling you that some even
будет я тебе говорю что некоторые даже
here who are in Europe and under the Russian
тут кто в Европе да под русским
embassy are even conducting an action like, you know,
посольством даже акцию ведут типа знае
arrest  Kadyrov Release this
арестуйте Кадырова Освободите вот этого
guy today, this is a bit of a weird topic for you
парня сегодня для тебя стрёмная тема
Well, it’s not weird But
немножко Да ну не стрёмная Но
damn, let him
блин пусть
sort it out, in short, it’s unpleasant
разбирается короче неприятное
Yes, damn it, damn it, this is normal for them,
Да блин ну блин для них это
that is, wait, let him
нормально то есть подожди пусть
sort it out, look stop, when were you
разбирается супр смотри стоп когда ты ты
with me last time you started the Maidan
со мной в прошлые раз начинал Майдан
legally illegally And  here and here you have it Yes,
законно незаконно А тут а у вас тут Да
let the court look into it Prosecutors Well, you did
пусть разбираются суд Прокуроры Ну у вас
n’t bother to look into the court prosecutor,
же не стали разбираться суд прокурор у
you had it all on a massive scale And
вас-то это было массовое всё такое А
here is an isolated case of a comrade who
здесь единичный случай товарища который
wants to do something there That
там хочет чего-то
is, about Yanukovych you
сделать То есть про Януковича ты
start there, everything is illegal  coup
начинаешь там э всё незаконный переворот
and that's it And here, in short, right away, I don’t know, but it
и всё А тут короче сразу а не знаю ну а
wasn’t some kind of legal coup. Well, you
какой-то законный был переворот не Ну
know, stop stop stop stop stop it
понимаешь стоп стоп стоп стоп стоп
was coming, look stop stop stop look
подо было смотри стоп стоп стоп смотри
again about Kadyrov, your stomach tightens and
ещ раз про Кадырова у тебя сжимается и
you say let the court sort it out
ты говоришь пусть разбирается суд
Prosecutors about Ukraine you  you don’t say: Let the
Прокуроры про Украину ты не говоришь
courts deal with Yanukovych.
Пусть по Януковичу разбираются суды
Prosecutors. Yes, you are starting to include philosophy here.
Прокуроры Да ты начинаешь тут философию
Why is that
включать Почему
so? Well, I’m telling you, the prosecutor’s court is just looking into it,
так Ну я тебе говорю просто разбирается
and what, what can I do?
суд прокурора а что что я могу сделать А
Why don’t you say about Yanukovych, like, let the
почему про Януковича типа ты не говоришь
courts deal with the
чтобы разбирали суды
Prosecutors, and then let the court and the
Прокуроры и там пусть разбираются судо и
prosecutor sort it out, but  they didn’t figure it out, what does
прокурор но они не стали разбираться что
it mean they didn’t, they
значит не стали они
figure it out
разбираются
Yanukovych Yanukovych filed a
Янукович Янукович подавал в
lawsuit I don’t know how he was tried for something, it’s
суд Я не знаю ну как его судили за чтото
not his su The European Court dropped all
не это его су Европейский суд снял все
charges against Yanukovych him What are the
обвинения с Януковича его Какие
charges The European Court didn’t bring
обвинения Европейский суд не выставлял
any charges against
никакие обвинения
Yanukovych Interpol him in this  in Rosk
Януковича Интерпол его же в этот в роск
they removed him then like he We are
убрали его потом типа он Нас устраивает
not satisfied with Yanukovych it turns out in this story
не Янукович получается в этой истории
the most
самый в
shocking people in the Russian Federation are all
шокола люди в Российской Федерации все
afraid of
боятся
Kadyrov
Кадырова
Why why Good
Почему почему Хороший
question
вопрос потому
because if I opened a session in front of you that
что если я сейс при тебе развернула
was under Dudayev,
которая при дудаеве была
it’s your business, let’s put it in short, let’s
тебя это твоё дело давай короче давай
turn it around to talk  I
развернёт говорить не
won’t And I’ll say Dudaev is the hero of Keri and
буду А я скажу Дудаев герои Кери а
Kadyrov Let’s have a sore subject for you today I
Кадыров Давай сегодня для тебя больная
won’t torment you
тема не буду тебя мучить
In short, old How
короче старая Сколь
tense I am How in Russia everyone is afraid of
напрягся Как в России все боятся
Kadyrov just damn it because there is no law in
Кадырова просто блин потому что нет в
Russia
России
Russia is a Somali state
закона Россия - это Сомали государство
404 ses there is no law subscribe to  miy
404 сес там нет закона подпишись на мий
Instagram I don’t know why this is for
Instagram Я не знаю для чого це тоб для
why you are there to marvel at the ocey face Ale
чого тоб там дивитись на оцей фейс Але
for you tse one two or three clicks Ale
для тебе це один два або три клика Але
you trimae mene and I will be kti Wow in me
ты тримае мене и я буду кти Вау в мене
there are a bunch of fouls and in me there will be a cool
там Купа фолов и в мене буде класный
mood so that it’s robiti but cool  video letter
настрий чтоб робити но крут видео пись
on my Instagram Popik Andriy
на мий Instagram Попик Андрий
otak Let me check for you
отак Давай я тебя